aaii.com 2017-06-06

# AAII: The American Association of Individual Investors

Our goal at AAII is to offer you the best investor education in a simple and secure manner via internet and print methods. As a publisher, we gather user and member information in order to provide an investor-friendly service. We have developed this Privacy Policy to inform users of AAII services about our privacy views and practices. This Privacy Policy is subject to change, so we recommend that you check back again in the future if you have any questions. 

**Site Usage Analysis**

To improve our website, we regularly track usage through log analysis to understand how our members and visitors are using the site. 

This information is used to determine popular areas of the site by measuring clicks and the length of time a member spends on a page. We keep track of this data for determining trends and statistics internally, and use this to improve the AAII user experience. This information is kept confidentially within AAII. 

**Use of Cookies**

AAII.com uses cookies to remember your login settings. This allows you to move through the site and certain member security points without any disturbance. Our site is set to keep you logged in for 60 minutes. This means that during a single browser session you can wander to any other site and come back to AAII.com and remain logged in. We are in no way extracting personal information through the use of computer cookies. 

Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can configure your browser to not use cookies. Please note that doing so will reduce some site functionality. 

**Protection of Your Personal Information**

AAII takes your privacy seriously and constantly takes the appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to your personal information. We've set up physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that keep your information safe. Data collection and storage processes on our secure servers are reviewed as necessary. 

**Email and Postal Mail Use**

We request your email address as part of the registration process for AAII.com. We use this information to contact our members and guest users regarding updates to the website and to personalize the service. Your email address is secure and AAII is committed to protecting your information. 

AAII maintains a subscriber list and will generally only send emails and paper mailings to users regarding AAII products and services, or to fulfill against a transaction initiated by the user. However, we do on occasion make portions of this list available to carefully screened companies that offer personal finance products and services that we believe may be of interest to those affiliated with AAII. AAII makes sure that any third-party service providers we use are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. If you do not want to receive these offers, please let us know by contacting AAII Member Services at (800) 428-2244. Office hours are Monday - Friday, between 8:30 AM to 5:00 PM CST.
